{
    "id": "ce6913b3f0b54d039dab5859e7fffd27",
    "title": "Prepositions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "See you ……………………………… next Monday.",
            "description": "Prepositions are usually dropped before expressions like next Monday or last Monday. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in",
                "No preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We entered …………………………… the church.",
            "description": "No preposition is used after enter.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "into",
                "No preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… what time does the train arrive?",
            "description": "Prepositions are usually omitted before what time...?",
            "answers": [
                "At",
                "In",
                "On",
                "No preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "One Mr. Samuel is ……………………………….. the phone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have read almost every novel ……………………………….. Dickens.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "by",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She hails ………………………….. a small town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He belongs …………………………… the local football club.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to the market …………………………… my brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You are responsible …………………………………. your actions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Please fill in the form ………………………….. ink.",
            "description": "We say in ink.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She stood ………………………….. him.",
            "description": "Beside means by the side of besides means in addition to.",
            "answers": [
                "beside",
                "besides"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He decided to quit his job ……………………………… several reasons.",
            "description": "for... reasons....",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "from",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}